{
  "response_code": 0,
  "results": [
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
      "question": "Townsend Coleman provided the voice for which turtle in the original 1987 series of &quot;Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles&quot;?",
      "correct_answer": "Michelangelo",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Leonardo",
        "Donatello",
        "Raphael"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
      "question": "Which cartoon family lives in 31 Spooner Street, Quahog, Rhode Island USA?",
      "correct_answer": "The Griffins",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "The Simpsons",
        "The Jetsons",
        "The Hills"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
      "question": "In &quot;Rick and Morty&quot;, from which dimension do Rick and Morty originate from?",
      "correct_answer": "C-137",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "J1977",
        "C-136",
        "C500-a"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
      "question": "In the 1969 Cartoon show &quot;Dastardly and Muttley in Their Flying Machines&quot;, which were NOT one of the lyrics in the opening theme?",
      "correct_answer": "Stab him",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Nab him",
        "Jab him",
        "Tab him"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
      "question": "What town was &quot;Springfield&quot; from &quot;The Simpsons&quot; originally named after?",
      "correct_answer": "Springfield, Oregon",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Springfield, Missouri",
        "Springfield, Illinois",
        "Springfield, Massachusetts"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
      "question": "In &quot;Gravity Falls&quot;, the character Bill Cipher remarks that &quot;the universe is what?&quot;",
      "correct_answer": "A hologram ",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "An illusion ",
        "A simulation",
        "Corrupting"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
      "question": "Who voice acted the character Hiccup in the movie &quot;How to Train Your Dragon&quot;?",
      "correct_answer": "Jay Baruchel",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Jack Brauchel",
        "John Powell",
        "Gerard Butler"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
      "question": "In &quot;Gravity Falls&quot;, how much does Waddles weigh when Mable wins him in &quot;The Time Traveler&#039;s Pig&quot;?",
      "correct_answer": "15 pounds",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "20 pounds",
        "10 pounds",
        "30 pounds"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
      "question": "In the &quot;Star Wars&quot; universe, what species is Grand Admiral Thrawn?",
      "correct_answer": "Chiss",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Gungans",
        "Pantorans",
        "Twi&#039;lek"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
      "question": "Which of the following films was Don Bluth both the writer, director, and producer for?",
      "correct_answer": "All Dogs Go To Heaven",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Titan A.E.",
        "Anastasia",
        "The Land Before Time"
      ]
    }
  ]
}